<u>cuong.trieu2207@gmail.con</u>

Phone: 093 526 4625

www.linkedin.com/in/viet-cuong-a92705182 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
C#.NET VB.NET
ORACLE
MS.SQL



# Trieu Viet Cuong

Dot Net Software Engineer Vietnam

# **Summary**

About me = {
isCSharpDeve

isCSharpDeveloper: true,

loveToWorkWith: ['HTML', 'JS', 'CSS', 'C#.NET', 'MS.SQL',

'Node', 'PHP', 'MySql'],

has Joined: ['FPT Software', 'Robert Bosch Engineering', 'CMC-

Global', 'Heineken'],

hobbies: ['Sport', 'Music', 'Photography', 'Technologies']

**}**;

Strong experience in development with 7 years working in the IT field Strong knowledge of .NET architecture

Knowledge of the Scrum process, team working, review code

Ability to think and Research to resolve the problem

Possess a Can-Do attitude, excellent communication, and problemsolving skills

# **Experience**

## **HEINEKEN-Tiger Tribe**

(09/2022 - current)

EKOIN– Development team

Customer	Viet Nam
Description	The loyalty platform helps to enhance the user
	experience for the customer, scan and redeem the
	reward
Team size	10
Position	Senior Back-end developer
Main	Implement back-end function
Responsibilities/	Host in UX interview/user testing session
Achievement	Work closely with agency teams, Global &
	Regional Product Owners to define the backlog
	and new feature
	Experience in interaction with: Openloyaly
	<u>platform</u> , <u>Gotit</u>
Technical	.NET 6, Azure: SQL, App service, Storyblok CMS,
	SSO, Cryptography, Webhook

<u>cuong.trieu2207@gmail.com</u>

Phone: 093 526 4625

www.linkedin.com/in/viet-cuong-a92705182 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills C# .NET VB.NET ORACLE MS.SQL

## UCA- Development team

(09/2022 - current)

Customer	Viet Nam
Description	UCA Unified Commercial App is an application that
	supports managing Sales promoters and effectively
	monitoring Activation activities in the field.
Team size	10
Position	Senior Back-end developer
Main	Implement back-end function
Responsibilities/	Integrate with the EKOIN project and third party
Achievement	Working with the data team and product owner to
	define the reporting model
Technical	.NET 6, Azure: SQL, App service, Blob storage,
	Google authentication, Hang-fire, Test Container,
	Fluent Validation

## **CMC-Global**

(12/2020 - 09/2022)

Intage AI – Development team

(1 year 6 months)

Customer	Japan
Description	Manage cutting industrial tools, manage and binding
	the coordinate defects
Team size	6
Position	Team leader
Main	Implement back-end function
Responsibilities/	Support technical to teammate
Achievement	Work closely with the project manager to provide
	the solution
Technical	.NET 5, Azure: SQL, Blob storage, App service,
	Service bus

## SMG – Development team

(03/2021 - 09/2022)

Customer	America
Description	The system that manages the customer feedback,
	generates the modernized report based on customer
	feedback
Team size	6
Position	Senior Engineer
Main	Implement new features to the existing system
Responsibilities/	Fix bug production
Achievement	Upgrade angular JS to typescript
Technical	Angular JS, Angular typescript, .NET Framework,
	MongoDB, Google Analytics (Angulatics)

Phone: 093 526 4625

www.linkedin.com/in/viet-cuonga92705182 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

C# .NET VB.NET ORACLE MS.SQL

# **Bosch Engineering and Business Solutions Software Engineer**

CI-CAT – Development team

03/2019 - 12/2020(1 year 9 months)

Customer	Germany
Description	ERP product manage user, role, asset, charging
Team size	6
Position	Developer
Main	Implementation
Responsibilities/	Support technical and mentor a new member
Achievement	Work closely with the Operations team for
	production issues
	Work closely with the Client for change request
Technical	.NET Framework, Oracle, VB.NET, Window Form,
	WCF service

Flexible Seat Booking project – Development team 12/2019 - 02/2020

(3 months)

Customer	Viet Nam
Description	Internal tool management and booking seats for
	employee
Team size	6
Position	Developer
Main	Implementation of the new feature of flexible seat
Responsibilities/	
Achievement	
Technical	.Net Core, Asp .Net MVC, MS.SQL, JavaScript,
	Ajax, jQuery, Web API

## **FPT Software**

11/2017 - 03/2019

P3.M35 – Function Development team

(1 year 5 months)

Customer	Japan
Description	ERP systems related to the asset, finance, and user with
	a large amount of traffic
Team size	200
Position	Developer
Main	Create a design document based on the function
Responsibilities/	specs
Achievement	Coding, Unit Test, Deploy
	<u>Certificate</u> of Merit from the Company's
	Production Director
Technical	.NET Entity Framework, Angular 4, MS.SQL,
	Web API, Active report

cuong.trieu2207@gmail.com

Phone: 093 526 4625

www.linkedin.com/in/viet-cuong-a92705182 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

C# .NET VB.NET ORACLE MS.SQL

# **Technical Skill**

- HTML, CSS, JS, Ajax, jQuery, Angular JS, TypeScript
- C# .NET, Web API, JSON, LINQ
- Unit testing: N Unit, Jasmine
- Design: Coding solid, Design Patterns, OOP
- Database: MS.SQL, ORACLE
- Cloud: Azure
- Source control: Git, SVN, TFS
- Tracking project: JIRA, CONFLUENCE
- OS: Linux(Fedora), Windows

# **Education**

Hong Bang University International HIU

Bachelor's degree, Information Technology (2013 - 2017)

# **Reference:**

Personal GitHub repo: https://github.com/vietcuong220795/